It's over, it's over, it's over, it's over, it's over, it's over.
Hmm.
He seems angry.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Yes, yes, yes...
When it starts, everyone who's watching the stream, let's all say "yes" and "no" together...
I'm afraid I'll make a boo-boo...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Thank you very much.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Well, first of all, cheer up!
I'm just a part-timer.
I'm a part-timer.
I've had a lot of recordings this week, but this one was amazing...
He was really firing on all cylinders. He was really firing on all cylinders. This week was fire week.
Everyone is saying "Fire" to me. Thank you very much.
Say "Fire. Thank you very much.
I want to do it, don't you? I'm happy.
I would do it, too, if you showed it to me. Without thinking.
I would do it. On TV, or rather, in front of the computer.
In front of the computer, or rather, in front of the computer.
I'm not surprised that I'm so quarrelsome.
Oraaa oraaa oraaa oraaa... Ostage says "water", so I say "oraaaa! Oraaaa! Why are you so angry?
I'm not sure why I'm angry... but the recording...
Master, may I? What day is it today?
What day is it today?
Oh, May 10th? I'm sorry! It's Cotton Day!
The best day of the year!
To be honest, it's used for noodles and many other things. .... Boo-boo, the whole country! Tsuchiyama Blessing, there are more and more important days!
I'm sure you'll have more big days ahead of you, but I'm sure you'll do your best.
Happy Birthday, Master!
The great land of the great land of the great land of the great land of the great land of the great land of the great land!
The big one's here! Yay!
I've never had anything like this before.
Looks delicious!
Wow!
HBD57
This is a new idol group.
There are 57 members.
57 idols.
That's amazing. Thank you very much.
This is a nice cake.
It's covered with gold leaf.
It's covered with gold leaf. I'll eat it from the side if you don't take it down quickly.
You told me earlier that I shouldn't eat it.
I'd like to have a devil's charge of Atamimin-san. I'm Manzer, sir, and I'm always happy to help you out from time to time. Lovely picture. Thank you very much. Can I ride this wave too?
Yes.
May I?
Excuse me. Excuse me.
What the hell, man?
Go! Move it!
Go! Go! Move it!
What? There was some kind of set-up.
That's why I didn't call anyone.
Nobody.
That's funny.
Thank you very much.
Happy birthday again.
Happy birthday.
Thank you very much. I got it. May I look inside? Of course. Thank you very much! Happy birthday again! Thank you! Happy birthday! Thank you!
Yes!
I got it.
May I take a look inside?
Of course, of course.
Oh, it's pretty heavy!
But what about the shape?
Mace-like.
Tattler!
Oh?
What's that?
Oh-ho-ho ho-ho ho-ho.
What is that?
Is that a Kamotsuru, or is that a Kamoshiki?
Brilliance, yes. Sake Mirai.
This is that sake! Wow, this is a good guy, this is definitely great!
Wow! So...
That's great!
I got this...
Wow!Wow.
Wow, this is some expensive booze.
Please drink it.
Thank you.
It's from Niigata.
Well, drink it today.
Oh, no.
Well, it seems like you're a master, so congratulations. Like that?
No master.
Congratulations.
Not at all.
By the way, EbiJu and the others just told me...
Yes, sir.
They gave me this.
Sake is in it.
I gave them fresh chocolates with sake in them.
Congratulations!
Yay!
You know what?
I think it's my autograph.
I think this is my autograph.
No, it's not.
It's not like I'm going to listen to the office, but...
Please don't.
I don't think so.
Devil's Charge is coming in fast.
Type 99, Master.
Etherae... that's right, Etherae... is exactly what I was born into on May 10, 1966.
I was born on May 10, 1966, in Nagano Prefecture... in Nagano Prefecture... where my mother's parents live.
I was born on May 10, 1966, in Nagano Prefecture.
That's the first word I said.
Ete-ra-yi!
She cried "eterai eterai eterai eterai" at the hospital.
And later, when I heard that...
This is exactly what I'm talking about now.
The first word I said was eterāy, and the first sound I made was eterāy.
More specifically, the first sound I made was "e".
The first word I said was eterai, and more specifically, the first sound I made was e!
E!
Aah!
Shut up!
Oh, I'll miss you.
Thank you all.
Happy Master's Birthday from Yuna, Niti, Obaigesu, Birthday Eterai, Moumoshimashite-san, Master Eterai Prefecture, etc.
I say, "I'm so glad you're here, Tera-ega!
I'm just saying that I'm glad that you're here, and I'm glad that you're here, and I'm glad that you're here. Congratulations to XSXHCX for being a master!
Thank you very much!
Thank you very much
How's your birthday?
No, no, no... it happens every year.
I don't mind if it happens every year.
You know...
It's like my birthday is something you don't even get to see.
Oh, really?
But this year, I don't know how it happened, but everyone was very considerate of my birthday.
It's a happy day, you know. So, let's get on with the show.
Let's get on with the show.
So, it's the weekend. Friday, the weekend.
What do you think? I thought you didn't have any food.
No, no, no, it's the weekend. It's Friday.
It's Friday. - Friday, Friday.
It's Friday. No Friday.
It's Friday... and Friday's not Friday... and Friday's not Friday...
He's always talking about "not trying so hard", because he usually watches the Epicchu family. Ai no te machine?
Really, I can't believe it.
So, today, I'd like to share some photos with you.
I received two photos from Serphone.
This is the first one.
This way, this way, this way, first of all, here it is, here it is, here it is, here it is, here it is, here it is, the venue of the concert.
Wait a minute, now that you're here, I'd like to share them with everyone who's watching the streaming video.
I'm going to stretch this out a little bit.
Okay? This is what the picture looks like now.
You're looking at a picture of me at a live concert.
I may look like this, but I'm singing and dancing.
I hadn't seen you in over a month.It had been over a month.
It's been more than a month since I've been back, but it's been a while.
I had a lot of gigs in a row.
And I had some things I thought I should do a little bit more
So during this one month period, I made some changes.
Oh, you mean like that?
Like muscle up?
I've been doing some physical training.
It's true... singing and dancing...
You have to have a certain amount of strength over here.
Strength.
After that...
I've been working on my muscles for the first time in a month.
My body was ready.
I'm not moving at all.
It's not what I would have said to myself.
It was a lot of fun.
I was soaked in the paint, and I was so happy to be able to do the show.
No, no, no, no. Let's take another one, shall we?
Yes.
And the other one?
The other one is the same live performance.
Even for those of you who have been following the distribution channel.
It's fresh, isn't it?
This one was for an event hosted by our office, Pyamo.
Is that Shingo next to you?
That's right. That's my partner, Shingo.
I have a partner.
We've been seeing each other a lot lately.
How are they?
We both have something in common.
We have something in common.
Really?
We're almost the same height.
We're only about one centimeter apart.
And we look the same.
Of course...
Sawapon is...
Sawapon, they call me a fresh clunker.
Ponkatsu is what they sell, right?
Shinko-kun...
At first, he's like a comedian.
He's a smart guy.
He's certainly smart.
But, he's a smart guy.
He's a clunker.
Really?
I feel like there are so many things to be picky about.
First of all, I don't understand what he wears or what he wears. From the clothes?
You know, there are those guys who are stylish and good-looking, but their clothes are a bit out of the ordinary.
That's right. He always says, "I'm going to be sharp.
He starts to look sharp in his clothes.
He gets sharp?
He doesn't usually say so.
I'm a bit of a jerk. I say things like that.
I used to make him wear old clothes with a BMW logo on it.
He used to wear clothes that no one would wear.
He's a weird guy like that.
I met him the other day.
He was kind of amazing.
He had a big face.
It's like he's wearing all kinds of shirts.
And his shirt.
He was wearing this really blue, beautiful-colored...
leather jacket
You know, like a leather jacket.
I don't know what that means.
We look like we're some kind of rapper's house, bought in the US, but we're not.
I'm so glad to hear you say "Pearl," because we've been together for 12 years.
We've been together for 12 years since we were in the 6th grade... and we always go out to eat next to each other.
I'm so happy to be able to go out to eat and we're always right next to each other...
I've spent the whole Ruden week in the snow
Pomfret is me, because I'm blue from the face
And the yellow one is my partner, orange
What's orange?
Honey-orange.
I see... I see...
It's the higher exchange for orange.
Honey orange is nice.
Never heard of it.
Honey orange is nice.Honey orange sounds great.
Looks delicious.
Well, well, well.
Do you do a lot of gigs?
Yes, recently.
I'm sure we'll be doing more in the future.
Is there a website or something I can check out?
You can find us on Twitter or Instagram, or Alibu, or something like that.
Yes, but the excellent Surfone is not just a clunker.
It's not just a clunker, it's the best weapon in the arsenal!
It's the best weapon.
You're not one of those guys, are you?
I'm talking, or rather, I'm like this... and when I start singing...
I think you guys are feeling it the most on the day, and it was amazing.
Well, well, well... let's see... let's hear from you.
First of all...
This is...
We've got a lot of good news, so I'll try to keep it short and sweet.
First, a picture of "Rasher Ramen"...
Thank you, Mr. Hidemi from Saitama, Japan... and good evening, Mr. Dandy Master, Mr. Bite of the Shrimps with the fresh Ryan 9.
I really wanted to try it on weekends because the lines are so long!
I got paid on a weekday and went to eat it!
Wow!
That's a great way to use your pay!
Ramen!
I went on a weekday before the restaurant opened.
But there was a 30 minute wait!
Wow!
So let's take a look at the picture first...
Wait a minute, please.
What kind of ramen is this? What kind of ramen?
I know what kind of ramen it is.
I think I got the wrong one.
May I?
Shall we?
Yes, sir.
Yes? Oh, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy, yummy.
Oh, yeah.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
It's a little transparent.
Shio Ramen?
I've actually had shio ramen in a restaurant.
Well...
It's very popular.
I think it's that one, right?
I think it's in Niiza, Saitama.
I think it's the most famous restaurant in that area.
Wow! Anyway, there's a long line of people waiting in line.
There's almost always a line. -Is that right? It's a very popular place.
You look like you want to eat. I want to eat!
There's a chance he's messing with the photo.
I'd like to try it too.
I'd like to try it once.
It was really good.
Well, first of all, you've just had it.
Yes.
It was kind of...
And one more food-related thing.
Yes...
This one is a little bit... you know how Ebiju-chan's live concerts take her all over the country?
Everyone and their family goes all over the country, so why don't we eat the local delicacies?
Yes, they send us a lot of information about where they've been, where they've been, where they've been to, etc.
I went to Nagoya for the spring tour of Ebichu and had a morning meal.
I'm sorry, you don't know?
Nagoya is famous for its mornings, but there are so many coffee shops in the city.
When you stay at a hotel there and wander around in the morning, you'll find that there are always morning coffee shops in Nagoya.
For example, this is a very inexpensive price, and you can get a cup of iced coffee and a piece of bread.
The price is very cheap, and you can get iced coffee and bread, and you can eat it like a toast, and there are cookies as an extra.
It's a panda version, you know. It's toast.
I'm not sure if the number of flunts is from Nagoya, but Rebekuchu from Sake Mihara City's Minami Ward, well, this guy really loves evetusions, and he went to see a live concert in Nagoya, and he wanted to try Nagoya food.
I wanted to try Nagoya rice!
I heard that there is a restaurant called "Nagoya Takachen, Nagoya Mei Gozen".
It's like all the local specialties are in one place.
First of all, here's a picture...
Wow, wow, wow, it looks so good! You can eat all of them.
I can eat all of it... this is probably the occasional Nagoya-Kochi chicken meat... lunch... yes, probably... ah, yes... miso katsu... earthenware miso katsu... indescribable miso taste...
the miso katsu is a very unique dish with an indescribable miso flavor.
I'm sure it's a big bowl of rice with a chicken and egg on top. It's delicious.
Yes! It's a selfie while taking a selfie.
That's right!I know, right?
That was amazing.
I want some!
Did you make yakitori or something?
Yes, I did.
So...
Okay, one more food-related thing.
Oh, no!
Stop it.
Well, this is... a little...
Yes...
This isn't Nagoya.
Yes.
Sendai! He probably went there on business on the night commuter rapid train.
Harch, the Sandwich Man, is a local fan of this famous Sendai specialty.
May I? First of all, it looks like this.
It's a triangle shape, and it's supposedly very tasty.
I'm sure you know people in Sendai. I'm going to bring it home and taste it next time.
I'll bring it home next time.
Buh-buh-bah-shih.
I'm sure you'll be able to grab it like this. I wonder if he'll show up...
It's a mess. It's like a cartoon.
I wonder if they'll come out...
Masashi Ueda is a famous cartoonist... and I made a poster of Kanna Rei Deville.
I drew Kanna Rei Deville in the style of a poster.
Izumi Aoi
He also draws a lot of pictures every week.
And this time, I made it look a bit like a manga.
Can I ask you something?
Wait a minute, there's another one in the style of a manga.
Oh, wait a minute...
I'm going to fill in the blanks with a cartoon style. Wait a minute. I just had a moment ago when I was thinking about Nagoya rice. So, please wait a moment.
Let's see, it looks like this.
Oh!
What is it?
You've seen this before, right?
Not Omonshan, what is it?
This is how they all look like.
Oh, my God! There it is! If this isn't a banda-jang, then what is it? They all look like this. Oh, there he is!
Oh, there they are!
Hey, this is the Bandai Race. This is Bandai Race Yande.
Wow!
This is a Varigata.
Oh, it's so tiny!
It's tiny!
Why?
It's not this tiny.
What was it? It's like a newspaper cartoon.
It's like a four-panel comic strip.
Yes, it is, isn't it?
Wow, amazing.
Wow, she's cute.
Let's just say, all of these faces should be the same, but I don't know how you can tell. Well, there's the hair and everything, but I've captured it.
Amazing.
I remember the feeling of the rainy season, when I got the shot in the morning.
Hey, what are you doing, rain on Tsuyu, rain on Tsuyu? That exchange was like the rainy season, like the second month of baseball.
What?
It's like this.
They're playing baseball.
What's that?
He threw to first base, too, for a 463.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much. So, there are a lot of good players.
It's hard to do it in front of all those people, but I'm going to draw a portrait of the person who's going to say the quotes in the quotes section.
Today, I'm very nervous.
What? Anxious?
Well... by the way...
Let's see...
Yu Necessity from Hachioji City, Tokyo sent me this quote by Shoko Nakagawa!
A quote from Shoko Nakagawa.
It's a quote from Shoko Nakagawa!
I love Shoko Nakagawa.
If possible, I want to draw her as pretty as possible.
I failed on about three pictures.
Not really a failure... more like a bad one.
I had you look at the failed Shoko-tan there, so let's see...
First of all...
Do you draw that one time, even if you are a master?Do masters usually paint in one session?
Yes, usually.
But Shoko once made her debut.
I'm sorry about that.
It's really hard to draw girls, no matter how many you draw.
I mean, it's really hard to draw girls, you know... how do you do it?
Why do you draw them so realistically?
It's all amazing!
May I have a word?
This was the first one... and the next one...
I'm not convinced.
So, can I have version 3?
Here it is!
Well, well, well... we're getting close.
He's from Nakano, Tokyo.
So you're from Nakano.
And you were born on May 5. It's the same Oishida.
I heard that Shokotan was hospitalized for a while due to health problems. At that time, he started watching Gundam and became addicted to it.
He was also into baseball, and even started watching soccer.
Hatsuko-tan has a lot of hobbies and interests.
Well, she is amazing, isn't she?
I don't have enough in my life.
I have a lot of things I need to do.
Well... I want more time.
I want more time.
I want more time... I want more time...
I'm not sure if I'm going to be able to do that, but I'd like to.
I'm not going to be over here, but it's still hard.
I'm not going to be a part of that, so it's still safe to say that I'm not a part of that.
I think it's time to end the distribution.
That's all for now.
I'll see you all next week.
I'd like to end with that one, wouldn't you?
That's it.
But I don't think that's it.
You know, that one.
You know, the one.
Okay, I'll see you all next week. Please do.
Yes, 3, yes, gandalfire!
See you next week!
Thank you!
Ha!
What?
Did you close it?
아!
Yes?
I learned했다!